conversionconference.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Conversion Conference Digital Marketing Event

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to ensure that Conversion Conference (we) interact with all of our customers in line with current legislation and in accordance with their wishes. If you have any concerns with how your personal data may be being used please contact us at privacy@conversionconference.com. We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. This information is used solely for internal marketing purposes and for the production of whichever event you have registered for. The only occasion when personally identifiable information is shared with third parties is when particular event attendee lists are made available to other attendees and sponsors of the same event. In those cases, the individual is given the opportunity to opt out during his/her event registration.

Orders

If you register for Conversion Conference, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form, which is hosted by a third party called eTouches. You must provide contact information (such as name, email and office address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for invoicing purposes and to fulfill your registration. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. Please refer to <http://www.eiseverywhere.com/w3c/policy.html> to view the privacy policy for eTouches.

Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information from Conversion Conference and its parent companies Rising Media and SiteTuners about related events or products.

Subscription Forms

If you fill out a form on our website requesting information about future events or speaking opportunities, we will use your name and email address to send the information to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.

Sharing of Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):

Conversion Conference collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website, or the websites and online services where we display advertisements (“Publishers”). This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve you and what ads you clicked on.

Any data used to serve targeted advertisements is de-identified and is not used to personally or directly identify you. We require third parties, including Publishers, to provide notice and obtain appropriate consent, where required by applicable law.

Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information

We only share personally identifiable information with Third Parties when particular event attendee lists are made available to other attendees and sponsors of the same event.

Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.

Google Analytics offers an Opt-out Browser Add-on that you can use to prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics, which you may access at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>. [Learn more about Google Analytics Privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html).

Technologies we use

Conversion Conference uses technologies such as cookies and pixels to keep track of your activities on our website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your device for an extended period of time. We use session cookies and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate and enhance the experience of our site, and to monitor and evaluate our website’s operation and use.

Conversion Conference and its advertising vendors such as Google, AdRoll, Bizo, Facebook and Bing may combine first party cookies and third-party cookies together to show you ads about Conversion Conference as you browse the web. Data may also be used from these cookies to inform us about the performance of our ads and how our ad impressions are related to visits to our site.

We use persistent cookies to keep track of your activities when you visit our website and to serve you advertisements about Conversion Conference as you browse the web. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. You may also decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.

  * [Opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and/or customize the Google Display Network ads you see](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)
  * [Opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and/or customize the Google Display Network ads you see](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)
  * [Opt-out of third-party vendor use of cookies via the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
  * [Consumer opt out page for the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)
  * [Opt-out of Facebook data collection via the Datalogix privacy page](https://www.datalogix.com/privacy/#opt-out-landing)

Links to Other Sites

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [privacy@conversionconference.com](mailto:privacy@conversionconference.com).

Business Transitions

In the event Conversion Conference goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Changes in this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.)

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@conversionconference.com](mailto:privacy@conversionconference.com).
